# 哈喽大家好 最近很开心
Hello everyone, I’m very happy lately
# 租了一个以前旧的山庄
I have rented an old resort
# 这个山庄放了两三年一直没有打理
This resort has been sitting here for 2~3 years without maintenance
# 所以我现在把它接(手）过来做些事情
So, I have taken it over to do something
# 这里可以看一下环境还很不错
You can see the surroundings are great
# 只不过就是荒废了一段时间杂草丛生
Just have been overgrown and deserted for a while
# 到时候我们再修整一下
We will trim it a bit by the time
# 正好今天厨房的师傅已经过来放地板砖
Right on today, the workers have come over to tile the floor in the kitchen
# 放完地板砖就可以进场
We can walk in there after they complete the tile work
# 好 我带你们看一下这里面
Alright, let’s have a look inside
# 一进来这里是一个桥
There is a bridge right after you walk in
# 桥下面有很多金鱼 这里面有很多金鱼
There are many golden fish under the bridge. Plenty of golden fish in there
# 而且我刚才看到有一条金鱼可能有一两斤
And I just saw one of the golden fish, might be two to three jin (1~1.5 kg)
# 黄色的金鱼很大
The yellow golden fish is very large
# 然后进来了之后这里是一个前庭 很宽
And here is the front space, pretty wide
# 看起来比较舒服
Looks very comfortable
# 这个大厅层高非常的高啊
This lobby ceiling is very tall
# 就是现在大夏天的话都一点都不热
It’s not hot here at all, even during scorcher
# 然后这个是玻璃的透光性特别好
And this is made of glass as it has perfect transmittance
# 然后这里原先的老板他设计得很好
The prior landlord had designed this place very well
# 他这边是进风口 一个水冷的
Here is a water-cooling ventilation system
# 然后那边后面有抽风机
And we have exhaust fans on the back
# 唯一的一个不好的就是这里面的
Only drawback here is that
# 以前的花花草草 现在都变成了大树了
The previous bushes have grown up to trees
# 我们来看一下这是什么树 具体我也不知道
Let’s see what kind of tree this is, I don’t know what exactly it is
# 应该是观赏树吧
Should be an ornamental tree
# 因为这里面层高特别高
Because the ceiling is way too high
# 所以它的灯没有说从上面吊下来
The lights aren't hung from the above
# 全部是做的这种路灯
They used this type of streetlight instead
# 这种路灯看起来感觉也不错
The lamp looks great, too
# 然后真正吃饭的厅在这里面
And the actual dining hall is right here
# 这里面可以摆差不多十几二十张桌子
It's big enough for around ten to twenty tables
# 还有边上的一些卡座
And some booths on the side
# 总共加起来可能 可以摆上三到四十桌
Add up to a total of thirty to forty tables
# 然后大家看一下这里有条沟
And here is a ditch
# 这条沟是他们设计来养鱼的
This ditch is designed to keep fish
# 到时候这里我也把它水放起来
I will fill up the water by that time
# 放起来养一些我们餐厅到时候能够做菜的鱼
to keep some fish that can be used for cooking
# 全部就养在这个里面 再养一些金鱼
All of them will be kept in here, plus some golden fish
# 然后看一下这边
And look at that side
# 这个有2468 有8个抽风机
There are 2, 4, 6, 8, eight exhaust fans in total
# 大家看一下这些桌子
You can see these tables
# 其实都是挺好的
are still good to use
# 我们做餐厅的这些东西虽然说你看着这是旧的很旧
Although these dinning tables look very old
# 如果你去买的话 特别贵
But still will be very expensive if you purchase them
# 比如这几张桌子凳子这里要花很多钱
For example, these tables and chairs will be costing a lot of money
# 这里有个亭子
Here is a pavilion
# 这个亭子应该是用来做观赏的
This pavilion should be used for ornamentation
# 然后这条沟从那边一直到这边有很长一截
And this ditch is very long, from there to here
# 这个厅大概有500个平方
This lobby is about 500 square meters
# 有500个平方 层高应该有六七米
Building height is about six to seven meters
# 就是进来了之后不会感觉压抑
You won’t feel oppressive when you walk in
# 现在我带大家看一下厨房
Next, let me show you the kitchen
# 看一下我们这里面
Have a look inside
# 师父现在涂这个墙已经涂到这边来了
The worker has already painted over to this side
# 然后那边的师傅在负责放砖
The worker over there is paving the floor
# 这里大概全部弄下来要两三天吧
It takes about two to three days to finish the pavement
# 要两三天 地砖放好了之后还要让它干两三天
Must let it dry for two more days after paving the floor
# 然后我们这些设备才可以运进来
Then our equipments can be moved in
# 这里还有一套厨具
Here is a set of cook stove
# 这套厨具也是以前剩下的
It was left by the previous owner
# 看起来是很旧 但是这个不是很旧
Looks very old, but it’s not that old
# 看起来旧而已 只是长时间不用有的生锈了
Just looks old, have a bit rusted after it has been sitting there for a while
# 到时候我们烧一点烧碱把那些锈就可以把它除掉
We will use caustic soda to clean it off
# 然后也可以用 我已经试过了这个灶是没有问题的
Then it will be ready for use. This stove was still functioning well last time when I tested it
# 我带大家去看一下二楼
Now, let’s have a look at the second floor
# 这个厨房的话面积有差不多100个平方米
This kitchen area is about 100 square meters
# 然后去看一下二楼
We are going to see the second floor
# 这些东西都是上一任老板留下来的锅碗瓢盆
These pots and pans are left by the last owner
# 这边是厕所
Here is the washroom
# 然后我们上二楼看一下
And we are walking up to the second floor
# 这个二楼非常的大
The second floor is very wide
# 就是下面是厨房
And the kitchen is below
# 这里是二楼 有个棚
The second floor has an awning
# 这上面应该用不上 地方太大了
This place is too large, I don’t think we are going to use it
# 总共加起来这里有厨房
Plus the kitchen below
# 加这个二楼加厅总共差不多有800个平方
And the second floor, tot up to approximately 800 square meters
# 然后我们还有其他地方
There are some other areas too
# 然后大家可以看一下这边
Everyone can have a look at this side
# 这边很宽的一块土 大概有一亩地
There is a wide piece of land, the area is about one mu (666.67 square meters)
# 然后我们也准备把它租下来
And we going to lease it as well
# 因为租金也不贵 一年也就几百块钱吧
Doesn’t cost much, a few hundred RMB per year
# 租下来种一点东西
Rent it for planting
# 我们这边就是把它做成一个中餐厅
We are going to make this place into a Chinese restaurant
# 就暂时不对外营业 我先自己尝试一下
It’s not opening to public for now, I will try it first
# 就是自己先弄一下
Just used for other things first
# 到时候的话可能也许会在这边拍一些视频也可以
Maybe we can shoot some videos here
# 然后接待一下粉丝也可以
or can be used to host our fans
# 这边因为这个厨房宽度够宽
Because this kitchen has enough space
# 以前我那个工作室嘛
The studio that I used to work in
# 因为地震了之后有一些风险
is a bit dangerous after an earthquake
# 就是它不怎么稳了 然后也比较小
It’s not that stable, and relatively small too
# 所以我想换一个大一点的地方
So, I want to switch to a bigger place
# 才能够更好地跟大家呈现一些好的内容
We can present some better contents in this way
# 我们这边外面的话还有个篮球场
We also have a basketball court right out there
# 有停车场 篮球场 还有养鱼的地方
There are a parking lot, a basketball court, and a fishpond, too
# 然后这后面的话 四处环绕的都是果园
The back is surrounded by orchards
# 有很多水果 这里环境非常好
Got plenty of fruits, and environment here is pretty well
# 然后从这里出去了之后是一个釜溪河
The Fuxi river is out there
# 围绕着这个这个山庄 围绕着这个果场
Surrounding this resort and this orchard
# 这个果场总共是400亩
The area of the orchard is 400 mu (~66 acres) in total
# 然后正好我们在这个中间
And we are right at the center part
# 中间的位置非常的好
The central location is excellent
# 之前的话他们是因为这个地方太偏了
Because this place is too remote,
# 然后又加上这个路也不好走
Also, it's hard to get here because of the bad road conditions
# 开车开进来也要开半个小时
It takes half an hour to drive in here
# 所以这里是一直放了几年
That’s why this place has been abandoned here for a few years already
# 现在我这边就把它接过来做一些我喜欢做的事情
Now, I'm going to take it over and do something I like